{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Termite Control Companies","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40355/":{"taskOID":40355,"originalTaskOID":40355,"setID":649,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5698,"questionDisplayText":"Service Need","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of termite service do you need? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6293,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Termite inspection","answerDisplayText":"Termite inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Inspection for Real Estate sale","answerDisplayText":"Inspection for Real Estate sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4398,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ongoing termite protection service","answerDisplayText":"Ongoing termite protection service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"One time extermination","answerDisplayText":"One time extermination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6296,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Termite property damage guarantee","answerDisplayText":"Termite property damage guarantee","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5699,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you see evidence of pest infestation or damage? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5494,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Saw swarming insects outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Saw swarming insects outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202085,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"House / Building exterior","answerDisplayText":"House / Building exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1843,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Deck or fencing","answerDisplayText":"Deck or fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Detached Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Detached Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3423,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Kitchen or bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen or bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":967,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement or crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Basement or crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7075,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wood framing, trim or furniture","answerDisplayText":"Wood framing, trim or furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5698,"questionDisplayText":"Service Need","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of termite service do you need? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6293,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Termite inspection","answerDisplayText":"Termite inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Inspection for Real Estate sale","answerDisplayText":"Inspection for Real Estate sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4398,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ongoing termite protection service","answerDisplayText":"Ongoing termite protection service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"One time extermination","answerDisplayText":"One time extermination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6296,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Termite property damage guarantee","answerDisplayText":"Termite property damage guarantee","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6293,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Termite inspection","answerDisplayText":"Termite inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Inspection for Real Estate sale","answerDisplayText":"Inspection for Real Estate sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4398,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ongoing termite protection service","answerDisplayText":"Ongoing termite protection service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"One time extermination","answerDisplayText":"One time extermination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6296,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Termite property damage guarantee","answerDisplayText":"Termite property damage guarantee","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5699,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you see evidence of pest infestation or damage? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5494,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Saw swarming insects outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Saw swarming insects outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202085,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"House / Building exterior","answerDisplayText":"House / Building exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1843,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Deck or fencing","answerDisplayText":"Deck or fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Detached Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Detached Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3423,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Kitchen or bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen or bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":967,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement or crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Basement or crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7075,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wood framing, trim or furniture","answerDisplayText":"Wood framing, trim or furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5494,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Saw swarming insects outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Saw swarming insects outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202085,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"House / Building exterior","answerDisplayText":"House / Building exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1843,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Deck or fencing","answerDisplayText":"Deck or fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Detached Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Detached Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3423,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Kitchen or bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen or bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":967,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement or crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Basement or crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7075,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wood framing, trim or furniture","answerDisplayText":"Wood framing, trim or furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40355/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40355,"taskName":"Pest Control - Termite","taskDescription":"Control or Inspect for Termites","xmTaskDescriptor":"Termite Control Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":344,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Control Eliminate Pest electronic removal","textMessagingName":"Pest Control Termite","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes the reduction or extermination of termites.","rolloverShortDesc":"Structural control or removal of household termites.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Control or Inspect for Termites.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Termite Control \u0026 Inspection \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Termite Treatment Companies","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":58,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Termite Control","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pest Control - Termite","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Pest Control Project","urlName":"Pest-Control-Termite","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Termite Control, Inspection Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Termite Treatment Companies","searchKeywords":"Control,Eliminate,Pest,electronic,removal,mitigation,exterminators,exterminator,exterminate,Elimination,Terminates,Termites","emcCategoryOid":-12057,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":649,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564373324358pwspr009F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}